Jeremy Hampden has a large circle of friends and is very popular at parties.
Everybody admires him for his great sense of humour -- everybody, that is, except his six -year-old daughter, Jenny.
Recently, one of Jeremy's closest friends asked him to make a speech at a wedding reception.
This is the sort of thing that Jeremy loves.
He prepared the speech carefully and went to the wedding with Jenny.
He had included a large number of funny stories in the speech and, of course, it was a great success.
As soon as he had finished, Jenny told him she wanted to go home.
Jeremy was a little disappointed by this but he did as his daughter asked.
On the way home, he asked Jenny if she had enjoyed the speech.
To his surprise, she said she hadn't.
Jeremy asked her why this was so and she told him that she did not like to see so many people laughing at him!